<archimate:BusinessProcess
    xmlns:archimate="http://www.archimatetool.com/archimate"
    name="Deliver Letter"
    id="51982187-e0ed-403f-9cbc-cc74c9d8a924"
    documentation="Letter is requested via Front-End or Back-End System&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;Inspire controls overall process of letter delivery from time when request is received to final delivery. Letter can be customized using Inspire Interactive. Every letter is automatically archived. This process also applies if single Statement is requested from Front-End.&#xD;&#xA;&#xD;&#xA;1.&#x9;Requesting System requests document via Inspire Scaler API providing letter parameters (customer ID, delivery channel, letter template, edit flag etc.)&#xD;&#xA;2.&#x9;Inspire Scaler requests data via Data Warehouse API using IDs provided in request&#xD;&#xA;3.&#x9;Based on the edit flag in request, Inspire Scaler:&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Edit Flag = True – modification of letter required, go to step 4&#xD;&#xA;•&#x9;Edit Flag = False – modification not required, go to step 6 &#xD;&#xA;4.&#x9;Inspire Interactive creates letter with customer data&#xD;&#xA;5.&#x9;Writer reviews and potentially modifies Financial Plan and then can:&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;•&#x9;Store Locally – store on Local PC or on Front-End, document is still Archived on OM side&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;•&#x9;Deliver to Customer – deliver to Customer via delivery channel (specified below, continue to step 6)&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;•&#x9;Delete – delete current letter&#xD;&#xA;6.&#x9;Inspire Scaler generates document using letter template passed in the request and data received from Data Warehouse&#xD;&#xA;7.&#x9;Inspire Scaler formats communication and deliver it via channel passed in the request:&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;•&#x9;Print – document is stored for Consolidation Process&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;•&#x9;Email – document is formatted (HTML without JS) and delivered via Email Gateway&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;•&#x9;Web Portal – document is formatted (HTML with JS) and delivered to Front-End, customer receives email notification&#xD;&#xA;&#x9;•&#x9;In Response – pass back to requesting system in response (only for Edit Flag = False)&#xD;&#xA;8.&#x9;Inspire Scaler formats (PDF) and delivers communication to Archive system"/>
